<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/" xml:lang="en" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
  <channel rdf:about="http://scej-home.playstation.net/j.home/RSS/locoroco/">
    <title>MuiMui Ship RSS(gb)</title>
    <link>http://playstationhome.jp/</link>
    <dc:creator>PlayStation®Home</dc:creator>
    <dc:date>2009-10-26T16:30:00+09:00</dc:date>
    <dc:publisher>Sony Computer Entertainment</dc:publisher>
    <language>en-GB</language>
    <description>Information</description>
    <image rdf:resource="" />
    <items>
      <rdf:Seq>
        <rdf:li rdf:resource="http://playstationhome.jp/" />
        <rdf:li rdf:resource="" />
      </rdf:Seq>
    </items>
  </channel>
  <image rdf:about="">
    <url>http://playstationhome.jp/</url>
    <title>PlayStation®Home</title>
    <link>http://playstationhome.jp/</link>
  </image>
  <item rdf:about="http://playstationhome.jp/">
    <title>&lt;font color=&quot;#33ffff&quot;&gt;Using MuiMui Ship (1)&lt;/font&gt;</title>
    <link>http://playstationhome.jp/</link>
    <dc:date>2010-02-04T18:58:20+09:00</dc:date>
    <description><![CDATA[<tab index="1"/><index page="2"/>Welcome to the MuiMui Ship!
This great passenger ship was built by the cute MuiMui from LocoRoco™.
Spend your holiday on the MuiMui Ship!

LocoRoco
- Dance near a LocoRoco and it will befriend you and follow along.
- Lead LocoRoco to the swaying grass and they will find Pickories for you!

MuiMui
- Dance to cheer up MuiMui when they are sad!
- Voice of MuiMui indicates their mood.

Pickory Insects
- Pickories are attached to Pickory insects.
- Try dancing near a flying Pickory insect!]]></description>
  </item>
  <item rdf:about="http://playstationhome.jp/">
    <title>&lt;font color=&quot;#33ffff&quot;&gt;Using MuiMui Ship (2)&lt;/font&gt;</title>
    <link>http://playstationhome.jp/</link>
    <dc:date>2010-02-04T18:58:20+09:00</dc:date>
    <description><![CDATA[<tab index="1"/><index page="1"/>Pickories
-Collect beautiful gems called Pickories, the currency in the world of LocoRoco™!
- Pickories can be exchanged for items at the Pickory Exchange.
- Pickories can also be obtained in the Loco Island personal space.

Binoculars
- Use binoculars to view activity in your Loco Island personal space.
- Also use binoculars to view progress of MuiMui construction on the LocoRoco™! playland.

Pickory Exchange
- Exchange your Pickories for wonderful items. Drop in every day to collect more Pickories!

LocoReverse
- This reverse game uses LocoRoco as game pieces.
- Players take turns placing LocoRoco on the board.
- Surround opponent's LocoRoco to reverse colour.
- Player with the most LocoRoco at the end wins!
- Enjoy the sweet LocoRoco movements!]]></description>
  </item>
  <item rdf:about="">
    <title>&lt;font color=&quot;#33ffff&quot;&gt;Using PlayStaion®Home!&lt;/font&gt;</title>
    <link></link>
    <dc:date>2010-01-14T19:25:20+09:00</dc:date>
    <description><![CDATA[<tab index="2"/><index page="3"/><font color="#33ffff">PlayStaion®Home</font> (hereafter PS Home) is a virtual online community which allows various types of players to safely meet, communicate, and play games with each other in a space that exists independently of specific game titles.

Players communicate with other players primarily by using <font color="#33ffff">lounges</font>. The MuiMui Ship is one such lounge. PS Home features many different lounges with motifs based on different game titles. Some lounges offer activities or games.

A <font color="#33ffff">personal space</font> is a room which belongs to a specific player.
Players may enter your personal space only by invitation. Your personal space is the perfect place to get to know your friends better, or to relax on your own. Many new personal spaces are being made available for purchase (new lounges are also being made available). Choosing an appropriate personal space can be a very personal experience, as it becomes the home base for your PS Home life! If you enjoy the MuiMui Ship, you may wish to consider adding Loco Island as a personal space!

When certain conditions are met in a lounge or personal space, you will obtain <font color="#33ffff">reward items</font> (attire, furniture, etc.). Also, various items are available for sale in locations within PS Home. Obtain unique items to create your own personal look! LocoRoco™ themed items are on sale now, and available for your perusal!

There are many ways to enjoy life in PS Home! The more people you meet, the more ways there are to have fun!
Create your own unique PS Home experience!]]></description>
  </item>
</rdf:RDF>
