<XML>
<!--********************************-->
<FLAG1>
8
</FLAG1>
<FLAGNUM1>
0
</FLAGNUM1>
<FLAG2>
0
</FLAG2>
<FLAGNUM2>
0
</FLAGNUM2>
<DAY>
1
</DAY>
<MONTH>
5
</MONTH>
<SENDER>
Undisclosed
</SENDER>
<SUBJECT>
Xi
</SUBJECT>
<CONTENT>
XI IS PRIVATE PROPERTY. DESIST FROM PURSUING IT IMMEDIATELY.
</CONTENT>
<!--********************************-->
<FLAG1>
14
</FLAG1>
<FLAGNUM1>
0
</FLAGNUM1>
<FLAG2>
0
</FLAG2>
<FLAGNUM2>
0
</FLAGNUM2>
<DAY>
24
</DAY>
<MONTH>
4
</MONTH>
<SENDER>
Jess
</SENDER>
<SUBJECT>
Blue
</SUBJECT>
<CONTENT>
Good work! But now tell me which color Newton says lies between C and D...&&Jess
</CONTENT>
<!--********************************-->
<FLAG1>
8
</FLAG1>
<FLAGNUM1>
0
</FLAGNUM1>
<FLAG2>
0
</FLAG2>
<FLAGNUM2>
0
</FLAGNUM2>
<DAY>
23
</DAY>
<MONTH>
4
</MONTH>
<SENDER>
Jachal
</SENDER>
<SUBJECT>
Yellow paper
</SUBJECT>
<CONTENT>
Hey,&Just to be clear - you need to find that yellow piece of paper. It could be anywhere in Home! So search hard.&When you find it, type what it says into your HoloPAD. It's worth a fragment!&Jachal
</CONTENT>
<!--********************************-->
<FLAG1>
8
</FLAG1>
<FLAGNUM1>
0
</FLAGNUM1>
<FLAG2>
0
</FLAG2>
<FLAGNUM2>
0
</FLAGNUM2>
<DAY>
31
</DAY>
<MONTH>
3
</MONTH>
<SENDER>
Thom
</SENDER>
<SUBJECT>
Hey
</SUBJECT>
<CONTENT>
Hey guys,&&Have you had a chance to check out Alpha Zone 1 yet? There are flying cows! Seriously!&&Thom
</CONTENT>
<!--********************************-->
<FLAG1>
8
</FLAG1>
<FLAGNUM1>
0
</FLAGNUM1>
<FLAG2>
0
</FLAG2>
<FLAGNUM2>
0
</FLAGNUM2>
<DAY>
30
</DAY>
<MONTH>
3
</MONTH>
<SENDER>
Thom
</SENDER>
<SUBJECT>
New Alpha Zone
</SUBJECT>
<CONTENT>
Amazing - you guys rock! Thanks to those who completed Stapler's "Foreign Language" expedition I've been able to get the pods working. These babies are straight out of the Enterprise.&&Step inside and it'll take you to the place you saw in the image. It looks like an alpha zone - an old uncompleted section of Home. We've already found a butterfly so it looks like Jess has been there. Is Xi here? Is it Xi? What do I know? Get in there and find out for yourself!
</CONTENT>
<!--********************************-->
<FLAG1>
8
</FLAG1>
<FLAGNUM1>
0
</FLAGNUM1>
<FLAG2>
0
</FLAG2>
<FLAGNUM2>
0
</FLAGNUM2>
<DAY>
27
</DAY>
<MONTH>
3
</MONTH>
<SENDER>
Thom
</SENDER>
<SUBJECT>
Jess247
</SUBJECT>
<CONTENT>
Hey,&Those of you who've been talking to Stapler will have noticed a weird text file in Jess's Documents folder. Well, a couple of people have figured out what it means - and I think it's something to do with that scrambled image 3lite managed to put together.&Anyhow, I think I might have figured out how we can get the teleport pods functioning... I'll work on it over the weekend.&&Thom
</CONTENT>
<!--********************************-->
<FLAG1>
8
</FLAG1>
<FLAGNUM1>
0
</FLAGNUM1>
<FLAG2>
0
</FLAG2>
<FLAGNUM2>
0
</FLAGNUM2>
<DAY>
25
</DAY>
<MONTH>
3
</MONTH>
<SENDER>
Huffman
</SENDER>
<SUBJECT>
Check out Jess247.com
</SUBJECT>
<CONTENT>
Huffman here, guys - I'm one of the alphaAFK. I've had a think about it and decided to give you access to Jess's online desktop. I shouldn't but it's the only sensible way to keep you informed. Go to www.jess247.com and find our chat there - for what it's worth! I've put a link to it on the Online Gateway upstairs.&While you're there... It looks like Jess has sent us a postcard. Take a look in her Images folder.
</CONTENT>
<!--********************************-->
<FLAG1>
11
</FLAG1>
<FLAGNUM1>
0
</FLAGNUM1>
<FLAG2>
0
</FLAG2>
<FLAGNUM2>
0
</FLAGNUM2>
<DAY>
23
</DAY>
<MONTH>
3
</MONTH>
<SENDER>
Thom
</SENDER>
<SUBJECT>
You've got mail... evidently
</SUBJECT>
<CONTENT>
Hey,&Now that you've come to grips with your HoloPAD, maybe you feel like trying something more adventurous?&Round the back of the teleport pods in the Hub is a robot called Stapler. He's gone kind of haywire lately, but it looks like he's had some tasks coded into him. Boot him up, and he'll give you some harder things to do - purely optional stuff if you've got a little more time on your hands and want a challenge. He's a devious little guy.&Play nice...&Thom
</CONTENT>
<!--********************************-->
<FLAG1>
12
</FLAG1>
<FLAGNUM1>
0
</FLAGNUM1>
<FLAG2>
0
</FLAG2>
<FLAGNUM2>
0
</FLAGNUM2>
<DAY>
23
</DAY>
<MONTH>
3
</MONTH>
<SENDER>
AlphaAFK
</SENDER>
<SUBJECT>
You've got mail... evidently
</SUBJECT>
<CONTENT>
Hope you enjoyed the whole guided tour. Thom isn't exactly with us anymore, but we've kept his automated voice in the Hub. You'll find out more about him when you're up to speed.&Now that you've come to grips with your HoloPAD, maybe you feel like trying something more adventurous?&Round the back of the teleport pods in the Hub is a robot called Stapler. He's gone kind of haywire lately, but it looks like he's had some tasks coded into him. Boot him up, and he'll give you some harder things to do - purely optional stuff if you've got a little more time on your hands and want a challenge. He's a devious little guy.&Play nice...
</CONTENT>
</XML>