<!--xil-signature: 016c4aa5661669199bab00206a20bbfafde1d24c-->
<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<xil ver="1.0" min-sys-ver="" anno="max-age=1200">
 <spc>
  <mtrl id="2000" lastm="2010-12-17T12:00:00.000Z" from="2010-12-21T22:00:00Z">
   <name>Music Unlimited powered by Qriocity™</name>
   <desc>Music Unlimited powered by Qriocity™ is a subscription service that allows you to enjoy your favorite music on your PlayStation®3 system, PC and other supported devices.&#xa;A catalog with millions of songs means that you can continue to enjoy your current favorites while discovering great new music through recommendations and channels organized by genre, era, mood, popularity and others. Music Unlimited also allows you to create your own library of music to share across your supported devices by importing songs from your existing PC library or by adding songs that you discover through the service.</desc>
   <url type="1001">http://xmb.dl.playstation.net/xmb/ps3/AD..1WSfwnwPwNFaQCpP5bBETOc_/music/sols/ICON0.PNG</url>
   <target type="u">psgm:play?id=NPIA09002</target>
   <package id="IP9100-NPIA09002_00-0000111122223333">http://qmusic.dl.playstation.net/qmusic/ps3/sols-music-v1.0.0.pkg</package>
   <cntry>gb</cntry>
   <cntry>ie</cntry>
   <lang>1</lang>
  </mtrl>
  <mtrl id="2001" lastm="2011-01-19T21:00:00.000Z" from="2011-01-21T22:00:00Z">
   <name>Music Unlimited par Qriocity™</name>
   <desc>Music Unlimited par Qriocity™ est un service à abonnement vous permettant de profiter de vos musiques préférées sur votre système PlayStation®3, votre PC et tout autre appareil compatible.&#xa;Avec un catalogue de plusieurs millions de titres, vous pouvez profiter de vos chansons préférées tout en découvrant des nouveautés grâce aux recommandations et aux divers canaux, organisées, entre autres, par genre, époque, humeur et popularité. Music Unlimited vous permet également de créer votre propre musicothèque que vous pouvez ensuite partager sur tous vos appareils compatibles en important les chansons depuis la musicothèque de votre PC ou en ajoutant les titres découverts via le service.</desc>
   <url type="1001">http://xmb.dl.playstation.net/xmb/ps3/AD..1WSfwnwPwNFaQCpP5bBETOc_/music/sols/ICON0.PNG</url>
   <target type="u">psgm:play?id=NPIA09002</target>
   <package id="IP9100-NPIA09002_00-0000111122223333">http://qmusic.dl.playstation.net/qmusic/ps3/sols-music-v1.0.0.pkg</package>
   <cntry>fr</cntry>
   <lang>2</lang>
  </mtrl>
  <mtrl id="2002" lastm="2011-01-19T21:00:00.000Z" from="2011-01-21T22:00:00Z">
   <name>Music Unlimited powered by Qriocity™</name>
   <desc>Music Unlimited powered by Qriocity™ es un servicio de suscripción que le permite disfrutar de su música favorita en su sistema PlayStation®3, PC y en otros dispositivos compatibles.&#xa;Gracias a un catálogo que contiene millones de canciones, puede disfrutar de sus temas favoritos y descubrir también otros muchos mediante las recomendaciones y canales organizados por género, época, tono, popularidad y muchos más. Music Unlimited también le permite crear su propia biblioteca musical para compartirla en los dispositivos compatibles importando canciones de la biblioteca de su PC o bien añadiendo aquellas que descubra a través del servicio.</desc>
   <url type="1001">http://xmb.dl.playstation.net/xmb/ps3/AD..1WSfwnwPwNFaQCpP5bBETOc_/music/sols/ICON0.PNG</url>
   <target type="u">psgm:play?id=NPIA09002</target>
   <package id="IP9100-NPIA09002_00-0000111122223333">http://qmusic.dl.playstation.net/qmusic/ps3/sols-music-v1.0.0.pkg</package>
   <cntry>es</cntry>
   <lang>3</lang>
  </mtrl>
  <mtrl id="2003" lastm="2011-01-19T21:00:00.000Z" from="2011-01-21T22:00:00Z">
   <name>Music Unlimited powered by Qriocity™</name>
   <desc>Music Unlimited powered by Qriocity™ ist ein Abonnement-Service, der Ihnen erlaubt, Ihre Lieblingsmusik auf Ihrem PlayStation®3-System, Ihrem PC und auf anderen unterstützten Geräten zu genießen.&#xa;Dank des mehrere Millionen Titel umfassenden Katalogs können Sie Ihre aktuellen Lieblingssongs genießen und mithilfe von Empfehlungen sowie nach Genres (Äras, Stimmungen, Beliebtheit u. a.) sortierten Kanälen großartige neue Musikrichtungen entdecken. Außerdem können Sie mit Music Unlimited Ihre eigene Musikbibliothek erstellen und diese auf unterstützten Geräten genießen, indem Sie Songs von Ihrer PC-Bibliothek importieren oder neu entdeckte Songs hinzufügen.</desc>
   <url type="1001">http://xmb.dl.playstation.net/xmb/ps3/AD..1WSfwnwPwNFaQCpP5bBETOc_/music/sols/ICON0.PNG</url>
   <target type="u">psgm:play?id=NPIA09002</target>
   <package id="IP9100-NPIA09002_00-0000111122223333">http://qmusic.dl.playstation.net/qmusic/ps3/sols-music-v1.0.0.pkg</package>
   <cntry>de</cntry>
   <lang>4</lang>
  </mtrl>
  <mtrl id="2004" lastm="2011-01-19T21:00:00.000Z" from="2011-01-21T22:00:00Z">
   <name>Music Unlimited powered by Qriocity™</name>
   <desc>Music Unlimited powered by Qriocity™ è un servizio in abbonamento che consente di ascoltare la musica preferita sul sistema PlayStation®3, sul PC e su altri dispositivi supportati.&#xa;Il catalogo con milioni di brani consente non solo di ascoltare la musica preferita, ma anche di scoprire nuovi brani usando i suggerimenti e i canali organizzati per genere musicale, periodo, stato d'animo, popolarità e altre categorie. Music Unlimited consente inoltre di creare la propria raccolta musicale e di condividerla con i dispositivi supportati importando i brani dalla raccolta già presente sul PC o aggiungendo i nuovi brani scoperti mediante il servizio.</desc>
   <url type="1001">http://xmb.dl.playstation.net/xmb/ps3/AD..1WSfwnwPwNFaQCpP5bBETOc_/music/sols/ICON0.PNG</url>
   <target type="u">psgm:play?id=NPIA09002</target>
   <package id="IP9100-NPIA09002_00-0000111122223333">http://qmusic.dl.playstation.net/qmusic/ps3/sols-music-v1.0.0.pkg</package>
   <cntry>it</cntry>
   <lang>5</lang>
  </mtrl>
 </spc>
</xil>
