<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ticker_text_1>
	<en-GB>   Welcome to the Xi Museum. Please feel free to explore the history of Xi, play some of the games, win/find 11 collectible items and don't forget to check out the Xi Museum shop for some great Xi items!   </en-GB>
	<fr-FR>   Bienvenue au musée de Xi. N'hésitez pas à explorer l'histoire de Xi, jouer à certains des jeux, gagner / trouver 11 objets de collection et n'oubliez pas de faire un tour au magasin du musée où vous trouverez des supers objets de Xi !   </fr-FR>
	<de-DE>   Willkommen im Xi-Museum. Schau dich in der Geschichte von Xi um, spiele ein paar der Spiele, gewinne/finde 11 Sammelgegenstände und schau auch im Xi-Shop vorbei, in dem es einige fantastische Xi-Objekte gibt! Benvenuti al museo Xi.   </de-DE>
	<it-IT>   Esamina la storia di Xi, gioca ad alcuni giochi, conquista/trova 11 oggetti e non dimenticare di dare un'occhiata al negozio del Museo Xi per alcuni fantastici oggetti Xi! Bienvenido al Museo de Xi.   </it-IT>
	<es-ES>   Explora aquí la historia de Xi, echa unas partidas, gana/encuentra 11 objetos coleccionables y no te olvides de visitar la tienda del Museo de Xi para conseguir fantásticos objetos de Xi.   </es-ES>
	<ja-JP>   Welcome to the Xi Museum. Please feel free to explore the history of Xi, play some of the games, win/find 11 collectible items and don't forget to check out the Xi Museum shop for some great Xi items!   </ja-JP>
	<ko-KR>   Welcome to the Xi Museum. Please feel free to explore the history of Xi, play some of the games, win/find 11 collectible items and don't forget to check out the Xi Museum shop for some great Xi items!   </ko-KR>
	<en-SG>   Welcome to the Xi Museum. Please feel free to explore the history of Xi, play some of the games, win/find 11 collectible items and don't forget to check out the Xi Museum shop for some great Xi items!   </en-SG>
	<zh-HK>   Welcome to the Xi Museum. Please feel free to explore the history of Xi, play some of the games, win/find 11 collectible items and don't forget to check out the Xi Museum shop for some great Xi items!   </zh-HK>
	<zh-TW>   Welcome to the Xi Museum. Please feel free to explore the history of Xi, play some of the games, win/find 11 collectible items and don't forget to check out the Xi Museum shop for some great Xi items!   </zh-TW>
	<en-US>   Welcome to the Xi Museum. Please feel free to explore the history of Xi, play some of the games, win/find 11 collectible items and don't forget to check out the Xi Museum shop for some great Xi items!   </en-US>
</ticker_text_1>