<LOCALISATION>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">Legal</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">\n\nTERMS OF SERVICE\nDownload is subject to the PlayStation®Network Terms of Service/User Agreement and any specific additional conditions applying to this item. If you do not wish to accept these terms, do not download this item.\nDownload is for use solely within PlayStation®Home by the purchasing PSN account. Content may not be used by any other account.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">\n\nCONDITIONS D’UTILISATION\nLe téléchargement est soumis aux Conditions d'utilisation / Accord utilisateur de PlayStation®Network ainsi qu'à toutes conditions supplémentaires concernant spécifiquement cet article. Si vous ne souhaitez pas accepter ces conditions, ne téléchargez pas l'article. Téléchargement uniquement pour une utilisation dans PlayStation®Home par le compte d'achat PSN.  Le contenu ne peut être utilisé par un autre compte.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">\n\nTERMINI DI SERVIZIO\nI contenuti scaricabili sono soggetti ai Termini di Servizio e Condizioni d'Uso di PlayStation®Network e a qualsiasi altra condizione supplementare specifica applicabile a questo scopo. Se non si desidera accettare questi Termini, non scaricare questo articolo.\nContenuti scaricabili dall'account acquirente PSN per utilizzo esclusivo in PlayStation®Home.  I contenuti non devono esser utilizzati da nessun altro account.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">\n\nNUTZUNGSBEDINGUNGEN\nDer Download unterliegt den Nutzungsbedingungen und Endbenutzervereinbarung von PlayStation®Network und jedweden für diesen Artikel geltenden Zusatzbedingungen. Wenn du diese Bedingungen nicht akzeptierst, lade diesen Artikel nicht herunter.\nDer Download ist ausschließlich zur Nutzung in PlayStation®Home und durch das PlayStation®Network-Konto. Inhalt kann nicht über ein anderes Konto genutzt werden.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">\n\nTÉRMINOS DE SERVICIO\nLa descarga está sujeta a los Términos de servicio y Acuerdo de usuario de PlayStation®Network y cualquier condición adicional específica que cubra este artículo.  Si no deseas aceptar estos términos, no descargues este artículo. Esta descarga es para su uso exclusivo en PlayStation®Home a través de la cuenta de compra PlayStation®Network. Ninguna otra cuenta podrá usar el contenido.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">\n\nこのコンテンツは、PlayStation®Network利用規約および個別条件に従って提供されております。\nご購入されたPSNアカウントにより、PlayStation®Homeの中でのみ、ご利用いただけます。</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">　</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">　</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">　</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">　</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">\n\nTERMS OF SERVICE\nDownload is subject to the PlayStation®Network Terms of Service/User Agreement and any specific additional conditions applying to this item. If you do not wish to accept these terms, do not download this item.\nDownload is licensed or sublicensed to you for use solely within PlayStation®Home by the purchasing PSN account. Content may not be used by any other account.</LANG>
	</PHRASE>

  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EXPORT_DETAILS</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Created by PlayStation®Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Créé par PlayStation®Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Creata da PlayStation®Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Erstellt von PlayStation®Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Creada por PlayStation®Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">PlayStation®Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">PlayStation®Home 제작</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">PlayStation®Home照片</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">PlayStation®Home照片</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Created by PlayStation®Home</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Created by PlayStation®Home</LANG>
  </PHRASE>

  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EXPORT_ERROR_TITLE</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Problem saving image</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Erreur de sauvegarde de l'image</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Si è verificato un problema durante il salvataggio dell'immagine.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Problem beim Speichern des Bildes</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Error al guardar la imagen</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">エラー</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">이미지 저장에 문제가 있습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">圖像保存時發生問題。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">圖像保存時發生問題。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Problem saving image</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Problem saving image</LANG>
  </PHRASE>

  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EXPORT_ERROR_HDDFULL</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">This image cannot be saved because there is not enough free space on the hard disk. Please make sure at least 512kb free space is available and try again.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Cette image ne peut pas être sauvegardée parce qu'il n'y a pas assez d'espace libre sur le disque dur. Veuillez vous assurer qu'il y ait au moins 512kb d'espace libre et réessayez.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">L'immagine non può essere salvata poiché non c'è spazio libero a sufficienza sul disco fisso. Assicurare la presenza di almeno 512 KB di spazio libero e riprovare.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Dieses Bild kann nicht auf Ihrem Festplattenlaufwerk gespeichert werden, da nicht genug freier Speicherplatz vorhanden ist. Bitte schaffen Sie mindestens 512 KB freien Speicherplatz und versuchen Sie es erneut.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">No es posible guardar la imagen porque no hay espacio libre suficiente en el disco duro. Asegúrate de que hay al menos 512kb de espacio libre e inténtalo de nuevo.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">ハードディスクが一杯です。空き容量を増やしてください。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">HDD 용량이 부족하여 이미지를 저장할 수 없습니다. 빈 공간을 확보한 후 다시 시도하십시오.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">HDD可用容量不足導致本圖像無法保存。請空出部分容量之後再度進行嘗試。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">HDD可用容量不足導致本圖像無法保存。請空出部分容量之後再度進行嘗試。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">This image cannot be saved because there is not enough free space on the hard disk. Please make sure at least 512kb free space is available and try again.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">This image cannot be saved because there is not enough free space on the hard disk. Please make sure at least 512kb free space is available and try again.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>

  <PHRASE>
    <LANG ID="REF">EXPORT_ERROR_GENERIC</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-GB">Sorry but we are unable to save this image.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="fr-FR">Désolé mais cette image ne peut pas être sauvegardée.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="it-IT">Impossibile salvare l'immagine.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="de-DE">Leider können wir dieses Bild nicht speichern.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="es-ES">Lo sentimos pero no es posible guardar esta imagen.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ja-JP">スクリーンショットをセーブ中にエラーが発生しました。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="ko-KR">죄송합니다, 해당 이미지를 저장할 수 없습니다.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-HK">很抱歉，目前無法保存本圖像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="zh-TW">很抱歉，目前無法保存本圖像。</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-SG">Sorry but we are unable to save this image.</LANG>
    <LANG ID="en-US">Sorry but we are unable to save this image.</LANG>
  </PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
