<LOCALISATION>
	<PHRASE>
		<LANG ID="REF">Legal</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-GB">\n\nTERMS OF SERVICE\nDownload is subject to the PLAYSTATION®Network Terms of Service/User Agreement and any specific additional conditions applying to this item. If you do not wish to accept these terms, do not download this item.\nDownload is for use solely within PlayStation®Home by the purchasing PSN account. Content may not be used by any other account.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="fr-FR">\n\nCONDITIONS D’UTILISATION\nLe téléchargement est soumis aux Conditions d'utilisation / Accord utilisateur de PLAYSTATION®Network ainsi qu'à toutes conditions supplémentaires concernant spécifiquement cet article. Si vous ne souhaitez pas accepter ces conditions, ne téléchargez pas l'article. Téléchargement uniquement pour une utilisation dans PlayStation®Home par le compte d'achat PSN.  Le contenu ne peut être utilisé par un autre compte.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="it-IT">\n\nTERMINI DI SERVIZIO\nI contenuti scaricabili sono soggetti ai Termini di Servizio / Condizioni d'Uso di PLAYSTATION®Network e a qualsiasi altra condizione supplementare specifica applicabile a questo scopo. Se non si desidera accettare questi Termini, non scaricare questo articolo.\nContenuti scaricabili dall'account acquirente PSN per utilizzo esclusivo in PlayStation®Home.  I contenuti non devono esser utilizzati da nessun altro account.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="de-DE">\n\nNUTZUNGSBEDINGUNGEN\nDer Download unterliegt den Nutzungsbedingungen/Endbenutzervereinbarung von PLAYSTATION®Network und jedweden für diesen Artikel geltenden Zusatzbedingungen. Wenn du diese Bedingungen nicht akzeptierst, lade diesen Artikel nicht herunter.\nDownload ist ausschliesslich zur Nutzung in PlayStation®Home für das erwerbenden PSN-Konto. Inhalt kann nicht über ein anderes Konto genutzt werden.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="es-ES">\n\nTÉRMINOS DE SERVICIO\nLa descarga está sujeta a los Términos de servicio/Acuerdo de usuario de PLAYSTATION®Network y cualquier condición adicional específica que cubra este artículo.  Si no deseas aceptar estos términos, no descargues este artículo.Esta descarga es para su uso exclusivo en PlayStation®Home a través de la cuenta de compra PSN. Ninguna otra cuenta podrá usar el contenido.</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ja-JP">\n\nこのコンテンツは、PlayStation®Network利用規約および個別条件に従って提供されております。\nご購入されたPSNアカウントにより、PlayStation®Homeの中でのみ、ご利用いただけます。</LANG>
		<LANG ID="ko-KR">\n\n[EMPTY]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-HK">\n\n[EMPTY]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="zh-TW">\n\n[EMPTY]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-SG">\n\n[EMPTY]</LANG>
		<LANG ID="en-US">\n\nTERMS OF SERVICE\nDownload is subject to the PLAYSTATION®Network Terms of Service/User Agreement and any specific additional conditions applying to this item. If you do not wish to accept these terms, do not download this item.\nDownload is licensed or sublicensed to you for use solely within PlayStation®Home by the purchasing PSN account. Content may not be used by any other account.</LANG>
	</PHRASE>
</LOCALISATION>
